Guide to the Evarts Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- William Maxwell Evarts, 1830-1901; Series II; 14.75 linear feet (36 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Hennessy, J., 1879 (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - Herrick, John J., 1881 February 25 (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - Hewitt, Abram S., 1883, 1885 (Box 11, Folder 194)
    - Hill, C. H., 1873 September 24 (Box 11, Folder 195)
    - Hill, Henry, 1884 February 25 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Hill (James K.), Wing, and Shoudy, 1881 March 3 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Hilliard, Henry W., 1880 May 22 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Hitchcock, Harry, 1884 February 18 (Box 11, Folder 197)
    - Hoar, Ebenezer Rockwood, 1884, 1893-1894 (Box 12, Folder 198)
    - Hoar, Ebenezer Rockwood, 1857, 1859, 1866-1891 (Box 12, Folder 198A)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/67
      See also: box 49B
    - Hoar, Elizabeth, 1884 May 30 (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - Hoar, George Frisbie (concerning efforts to locate papers of Roger Sherman), 1893-1895 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Hoar, Helen, 1893 September 6 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Hoar, Ruth A., 1893, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Hoar, Samuel, 1890 November 23 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Hoffman, Wickham, 1885 February 16 (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Holland, Caroline, Undated (c. 1864) (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Holland, Francis J., 1876 September 4 (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Holmes, Artemas H., 1882 April 17 (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Homes, Henry A., 1885 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 203)
    - Horton, J. Dana, 1881-1882, 1888 (Box 12, Folder 204)
    - Hounslow, William E., 1886 November 23 (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Howe, Timothy Otis (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Hoyt, Alfred M., 1884 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Hoyt, John W., 1895 (Box 12, Folder 206)
    - Hubbard, Thomas H. (Butler, Stillman, and Hubbard), 1883, 1884 (Box 12, Folder 207)
    - Hubbell, J. A., 1880 October 29 (Box 12, Folder 208)
    - Hubbell, Walter S., 1885 March 14 (Box 12, Folder 208)
    - Huffman, Walter A., 1895 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 208)
    - Hughes, Bela M., 1885 January 11 (Box 12, Folder 209)
    - Hughes, Thomas, 1864 March 3 (Box 12, Folder 209)
    - Hunt, Ward, 1880 March 8 (Box 12, Folder 209)
    - Hunter, William, 1880 May 25 (Box 12, Folder 210)
    - Hunton, Eppa, 1880 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 210)
    - Hurd, Charles Edwin, 1885 February 28 (Box 12, Folder 210)
    - Hurlbert, William Henry, 1880-1881, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 211)
    - Hurlbut, Stephen Augustus (in re: death of Jeremiah Evarts), 1877 (Box 12, Folder 212)
    - Hyde, E. F. (Box 12, Folder 212)
      See: box 13, folder 261
    - Interior, (United States) Department of the, 1887 November 19 (Box 12, Folder 213)
    - International Monetary Conference, 1881-1882 (Box 12, Folder 214-216)
    - Ireland, John B., 1883 March 17 (Box 12, Folder 217)
    - James, Darwin Rush, 1886 (Box 12, Folder 218)
    - James, Thomas L., 1879 November 26 (Box 12, Folder 218)
    - Jemot, Charles, 1877 June 8 (Box 12, Folder 219)
    - Jennings, F. B., 1891 July 1 (Box 12, Folder 219)
    - Johnson, Alexander S., 1865 September 21 (Box 12, Folder 220)
    - Johnson, Paul E., 1889, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 220)
    - Johnson, William Preston, 1879 August 12 (Box 12, Folder 220)
    - Jones, Julia Clinton, 1881 January (Box 12, Folder 220)
    - Kasson, John Adam, 1878, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 221)
    - Kaufmann, Sigismund, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 222)
    - Keller, Matthew (in re: Tajuta Ranch case), 1879 (Box 12, Folder 223)
    - Kellogg, William Pitt, 1880 May 4 (Box 12, Folder 224)
    - Kent, George R., 1885 March 2 (Box 12, Folder 224)
    - Kidd, E. E., 1881 December 16 (Box 12, Folder 224)
    - Kilbourne and Latta (real estate and note brokers), 1873 (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - King, Horatio C. (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - King, O. K., 1880 October 20 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - King, R. H., 1880 September 14 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - Kip, William Ingraham, 1880 February 17 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - Knox, Jonathan Day, 1881 March 22 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - Kraus, Dr. J., 1889 October 9 (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - Krauss, E. E., 1881 February 14 (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - Kruse, F. W., 1885 March 23 (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - Lamson, M. W., 1880 November 11 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - Lapham, Elbridge Gerry, 1885 March 9 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - Laune, Sylvester, 1880 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - Law, S. D., 1875 September 14 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - Lawrence, Marie D., 1880 (Box 12, Folder 229)
    - Lawrence, W. B., 1880 May 9 (Box 12, Folder 230)
    - Lee and Company D. W. Lee, W. Creighton Lee), 1868-1870 (Box 12, Folder 231)
      Letters To WME/From WME:ca. 10/2
    - Lee and Company (D. W. Lee, W. Creighton Lee), 1871-1883 (Box 12, Folder 232)
      Letters To WME/From WME:ca. 10
    - Legari, Alice B., n.y. March 29 (Box 12, Folder 233)
    - Lehman, J. and M., 1891 January 9 (Box 12, Folder 233)
    - Leonard, Joseph C., 1885 March 28 (Box 12, Folder 233)
    - Lesser, Maximus A., 1890 October 3 (Box 12, Folder 234)
    - Lewis, Robert, 1881 July 8 (Box 12, Folder 234)
    - Lewis, S., 1881 February 4 (Box 12, Folder 234)
    - Leupp, Isabella W., 1880-1881, undated (Box 12, Folder 235)
    - Leupp, Laura T., 1885 (Box 12, Folder 235)
    - London: Athenaeum, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 236)
    - London: Reform Club, Frederic W. Hasford, 1864 February 20 (Box 13, Folder 236)
    - Lord, Joseph E., 1885 March 23 (Box 13, Folder 237)
    - Lord and Taylor, 1885 January 16 (Box 13, Folder 237)
    - Loring, Edward G., 1887 January 28 (Box 13, Folder 237)
    - Loring, Harriet B., 1880 September 17 (Box 13, Folder 237)
    - Lossing, Benson J., 1882 December 5 (Box 13, Folder 238)
    - Louis, Alfred H., 1872-1876 (Box 13, Folder 239)
      Letters To WME/From WME:5/1
    - Louisiana Democratic Anti-Lottery State Executive Committee, 1890 December 24 (Box 13, Folder 240)
    - Low, Seth, 1880, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 241)
    - Lowe, Ralph Phillips, 1882-1883 (Box 13, Folder 242)
    - Lowell, James Russell, 1881 (Box 13, Folder 243)
      Letters To WME/From WME:3/1
    - Ludlow (E. H.) and Company, 1881 February 5 (Box 13, Folder 244)
    - Lush, Robert, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 245)
    - Lynwood, Harold, 1864 August 22 (Box 13, Folder 245)
    - Lyon, C. Burton Phillips, 1891, undated (Box 13, Folder 246)
    - McAllister, Ward, 1886 December 18 (Box 13, Folder 247)
    - McCarter, D. B., 1885 April 1 (Box 13, Folder 248)
    - McCormick, Richard Cunningham, 1881 January 28 (Box 13, Folder 248)
    - McCrary, George W., 1879 July 11 (Box 13, Folder 249)
    - MacDougall, C. D., 1881 January 18 (Box 13, Folder 250)
    - MacFarland, W. W., 1881 February 15 (Box 13, Folder 250)
    - McKenney, James H., 1881, 1882 (Box 13, Folder 250)
    - McKeon, John, 1869 December 16 (Box 13, Folder 251)
    - McPherson, John Rhoderic, 1881 February 1 (Box 13, Folder 252)
    - MacRay, Henrietta and Margaret, 1891, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 253)
    - MacVeagh, Wayne, 1880 (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - Magnin, Pierre Joseph (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - Manning, J. L., 1877 March 29 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - Marley, J. W., 1881 January 14 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - Marshall, D. D. T., 1881 January 28 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Marshall, Henry Rutgers, 1881 January 24 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Martin, H. M., 1881, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Mason and Smith, 1884 February 27 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Matchett, W. B., 1881, 1887 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Mathewson, Harriet S., 1885 January 15 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Matteson, O. B., 1879-1880 (Box 13, Folder 258)
    - Matthews, (H?) Morrison, n.y. March 19 (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - Matthews, Stanley, 1883 August 19 (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - Mayhew, J. E., 1879 August 13 (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - Merrill, P., 1885 March 11 (Box 13, Folder 260)
    - Merritt, Edwin A., 1879 (Box 13, Folder 261)
    - Merwin, Samuel, n.y. January 29 (Box 13, Folder 262)
    - Metropolitan Gas Light Company, 1869 March 1 (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Waldo S. Pratt, 1880 October 5 (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Metropolitan Steamship Company, 1891 January 5 (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Mexican Telegraph Company, James A. Scrymser, 1882 April 28 (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - Miller, George Douglas, 1880 September 17 (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Miller, S. C., 1880 May 15 (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Mills, Abby Burrill, 1864 December 9 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Mitchell, George W., 1895 July 13 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Mitchell, W. A., 1878 August 14 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Montgomery, J. Eglinton, 1880, 1882 (Box 13, Folder 267)
    - Morgan, Homer, 1876, 1881 (Box 13, Folder 268)
    - Morgan, P. H., 1880 (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - Morrill, Justin S., 1895 (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Morris, Hariette Hall, 1879 October 17 (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Morris, L. G., 1879 October 28 (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Morton, Howard, 1895 December 14 (Box 13, Folder 271)
    - Morton Monumental Association, 1882 April 21 (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Moulton, Caroline Chase, 1881 January 31 (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Munson and Phillip, attorneys at law, 1876 April 6 (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Murray, Jacob B., (1879) December 3 (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Murphy, Anna L., 1869, 1870 (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - Myers, Leonard, 1891 February 21 (Box 13, Folder 275)
    - Nash, Stephen P., 1880 September 8 (Box 13, Folder 276)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers (Box 13, Folder 276)
      See: box 16, folder 415
    - National Republican Vigilant Association, 1895 June 29 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - National Union League, Thomas G. Baker, 1885 March 12 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - National Ventilating Company, E. E. Rice, 1880 September 20 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - New York and Brooklyn Bridge, Trustees of the, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 278)
    - New York City: Fourth National Bank, 1881 October 28 (Box 13, Folder 279)
    - New York City Hamilton Republican Club, 1890 December 10 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - New York City Harlem Republican Club, 1891 February 9 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - New York City Lincoln Republican Club, 1890 December 20 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - New York City Republican Club, 1895 June 6 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - New York City: Union League Club, 1867-1868, 1881-1885 (Box 13, Folder 281)
    - New York Bar Association (Box 13, Folder 281)
      See: box 14, folder 349
    - New York Mercantile Exchange, 1890, 1891 (Box 13, Folder 282)
    - New York Press, J. W. Muller, 1895 October 18 (Box 13, Folder 282)
    - Der New York Republikaner, J. C. F. Beyland, 1885 January 27 (Box 13, Folder 282)
    - New York, State of: (Box 13, Folder 283)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1885 December 11 (Box 13, Folder 283)
      - Executive Chamber, 1875 November 30 (Box 13, Folder 283)
    - Newlin, A. P., 1880 January 15 (Box 13, Folder 284)
    - Nicholson, James William Augustus, 1881 January 26 (Box 13, Folder 284)
    - Nordhoff, Charles, 1880-1881, 1883-1884 (Box 13, Folder 285)
    - North American Review (Box 13, Folder 285)
      See: box 9, folder 65
    - Northrop, Birdsey Grant, 1881 January 28 (Box 13, Folder 286)
    - Noyes, Edward F., Undated (c. 1881) (Box 13, Folder 287)
    - O'Conor, Charles, 1860, undated (Box 13, Folder 288)
    - O'Gorman, Richard, 1866 September 13 (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - Old Dominion Steamship Company, 1891 January 12 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - Oliphant, R., 1880 July 21 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - O'Neil, William T., 1885 February 12 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - Oregon Railway, and Navigation Company, 1880, 1881 (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - Ormsby Brothers and Company, 1878, 1882 (Box 13, Folder 292)
    - Osten, Jos., 1881 October 25 (Box 13, Folder 293)
    - Owen, Allen F., 1848, 1858 (Box 13, Folder 294)
    - Owen, Edward L., 1879 September 23 (Box 13, Folder 295)
    - Owen, Sue Hamilton, 1880-1889 (Box 13, Folder 295)
    - Owen and Vose, 1859 April 22 (Box 13, Folder 295)
    - Paine, W. H., 1880 (Box 14, Folder 296)
    - Palmer, O. H., 1880 December 21 (Box 14, Folder 297)
    - Parker, Cortlandt, 1881-1882 (Box 14, Folder 298)
    - Parker, H. W., 1883 March 20 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Parsons, H. C., 1887 February 26 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Patterson, E. W., 1880 March 20 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Patterson, J. M. and Amelia W., 1894 January 11 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Paulison, C. M. K., 1881 January 31 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Paulison, John P., 1880 February 27 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Pavey, Darwin C., 1884, 1885 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Peabody Education Fund (Box 14, Folder 300)
      See: box 9, folder 98 See: box 11, folder 151 See: box 11, folder 160 See: box 13, folder 286 See: box 14, folder 328 See: box 16, folder 432 See: box 16, folder 443
    - Peabody, Charles A., 1881 January 19 (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Peddrick, Frances B., 1895 June 1 (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Perkins, Charles Bruen, 1891 October 17 (Box 14, Folder 302)
    - Perkins, Charles C., 1880-1881 (Box 14, Folder 303)
    - Perkins, Edward N., 1882 February 20 (Box 14, Folder 304)
    - Perkins, Edward Newton (grandson), 1888 January 16 (Box 14, Folder 304)
    - Peters, Bernard (Box 14, Folder 304)
      See: box 9, folder 62
    - Phelps, Edward John, 1882 March 18 (Box 14, Folder 305)
    - Phelps, James (Box 14, Folder 305)
    - Phelps, Royal, 1860 March 16 (Box 14, Folder 305)
    - Philipp, M. B., 1881 November 7 (Box 14, Folder 306)
    - Pierrepont, Edwards, 1879 May 22 (Box 14, Folder 307)
    - Pierson, H. W., 1880 September 13 (Box 14, Folder 307)
    - Pike, Chester, 1882, 1885 (Box 14, Folder 308)
    - Pitkin,(Peter) and Son, 1891 January (Box 14, Folder 309)
    - Platt, Emily, 1878 June 19 (Box 14, Folder 309)
    - Pomeroy, J. P., 1880 October 12 (Box 14, Folder 310)
    - Porter, Edmund J., 1879, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 311)
    - Porter, Fitz John, 1885 October 12 (Box 14, Folder 311)
    - Porter, Noah, 1853, 1877-1883 (Box 14, Folder 312)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/4
    - Potter, Henry Codman, 1895, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 313)
    - Potter, Horatio, 1880 April (Box 14, Folder 313)
    - Prescott, Cyrus D., 1885 March 28 (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - Preston, Nathan Evarts, 1900 January 25 (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - Price, J. A., 1883 March 5 (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - Prichard, William M., 1879-1895 (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - Prince, L. Bradford, 1880 March 4 (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - Puleston, J. H., 1885 January 20 (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Putnam, F. C., 1880, 1882 (Box 14, Folder 317)
    - Putnam, James Osborne, 1874-1899 (Box 14, Folder 318)
    - Quinn, Timothy, 1880 February 21 (Box 14, Folder 319)
    - Rapallo, Edward, 1883 March 30 (Box 14, Folder 320)
    - Rayner, Kenneth, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 321)
    - Rayner, Mrs. Kenneth, 1880 July 25 (Box 14, Folder 321)
    - Redfield, A. A., 1879, 1882 (Box 14, Folder 322)
    - Reed, Edgar H., 1885 January 26 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - Reed, T. B., 1894 February 3 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - Reeve, Felix A., 1880 June 12 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - Reeve, Henry, 1864 February 17 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - Reid, Samuel C., 1887 January 11 (Box 14, Folder 324)
    - Reid, Whitelaw, 1880 September 5 (Box 14, Folder 324)
    - Reynolds, A. E., 1886 January 11 (Box 14, Folder 325)
    - Rice, William Whitney, 1880 May 4 (Box 14, Folder 326)
    - Richards, William M., [1886?] January 22 (Box 14, Folder 327)
    - Riggs, George W., 1881 (Box 14, Folder 328)
    - Risley, H. A., 1880, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 329)
    - Ritter and Wimer, 1887 October 7 (Box 14, Folder 330)
    - Robinson, W. E., 1880 January 19 (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - Robson, W. O., 1880 September 23 (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - R(ockwell?), F. T., 1881 October 3 (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - Rodgers, James F., 1884 January 25 (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - Rogers, Sherman S., 1879 May 2 (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - Roget, Aimée, 1879, 1887, 1888 (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1884 January 8, undated (Box 14, Folder 333)
    - Root and Tinker, The American Exporter, 1885 March 20 (Box 14, Folder 334)
    - Ropes, Ripley, 1879-1880 (Box 14, Folder 335)
    - Rothery, Henry Cadogan, 1864 (Box 14, Folder 336)
    - Royall, William L., 1885 March 14 (Box 14, Folder 337)
    - Russell, Charles (Lord Russell of Killowen) (Box 14, Folder 338)
      - Excerpts from a travel journal relating to William Maxwell Evarts, 1883 (Box 14, Folder 338)
    - ALS (2), 1884 June 1, 1896 October 3 (Box 14, Folder 338)
    - Russell, William, 1885 March 30 (Box 14, Folder 339)
    - St. Hilaire, Barthelemy, 1881 April 30 (Box 14, Folder 340)
    - St. John, William P., 1886 (Box 14, Folder 341)
    - Sanders, Frank Knight, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 342)
    - Sandford, Alice, 1879 December 13 (Box 14, Folder 343)
    - Sanford, Henry S., 1880, 1883 (Box 14, Folder 343)
    - San Marzano, L. de (marquise), 1883, undated (Box 14, Folder 344)
    - Scarborough, G. L., 1881 December 9 (Box 14, Folder 345)
    - Scarborough, W. S., 1880 July 12 (Box 14, Folder 345)
    - Scarborough, Mrs. W. S., 1880 September 11 (Box 14, Folder 345)
    - Schlözer, Kurd von, 1879, 1881, n.y. (Box 14, Folder 346)
    - Schurz, Carl, 1880 June 4 (Box 14, Folder 347)
    - Schuyler, Eugene, 1884 January 31 (Box 14, Folder 348)
    - Scranton, Charles, (Evarts genealogy), 1883 March 3 (Box 14, Folder 348)
    - Scribner, John M., 1881-1882 (Box 14, Folder 349)
    - Scudder, Charles D. (son-in-law), 1884 June 10 (Box 14, Folder 350)
    - Scudder, Henry J., 1880 July 6 (Box 14, Folder 350)
    - Scudder, Horace E., 1884 March 1 (Box 14, Folder 350)
    - Scudder, Louisa Wardner (Evarts) (daughter), 1895 October 29 (Box 14, Folder 350)
    - [Searle?], C. P., 1877 January 13 (Box 14, Folder 351)
    - Seaver, William A., 1880 (Box 14, Folder 351)
    - Sedgwick, Henry D., 1878 December 21 (Box 14, Folder 351)
    - Senior, (Mary Charlotte Mair?), 1864 March 5 (Box 14, Folder 352)
    - Serrell, Edward W., 1880 June 1 (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Sessions, Loren B., 1880 (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Seward, Clarence A., 1882, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Seward, Frederic William, 1880 May 31 (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Seward, Olive Risley, 1876 September 23, 1880 January (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Seward, William Henry, 1864 (Box 14, Folder 355)
    - Shaw, Charles P. (Box 14, Folder 355)
      See: box 29, folders 580-581
    - Shearman, Thomas G., 1879 (Box 15, Folder 356)
    - Shepard, Elliott F., 1880 December 23 (Box 15, Folder 356)
    - Sherman, Edward S., 1879 July 21 (Box 15, Folder 357)
    - Sherman, Ellen E., 1883 January 8 (Box 15, Folder 357)
    - Sherman, F. R., 1859 January 29 (Box 15, Folder 357)
    - Sherman, Isaac, 1880 June 14 (Box 15, Folder 358)
    - Sherman, J. Howard, 1879 June 25 (Box 15, Folder 358)
    - Sherman, John S., 1879, 1880 (Box 15, Folder 358)
    - Sherman, Rachel, 1881 (Box 15, Folder 359)
    - Sherman, Roger M., 1880 September 28 (Box 15, Folder 359)
    - Sherman, Roger, correspondence concerning efforts to collect his papers (Box 15, Folder 359)
      See: box 12, folder 200
    - Sherman, William Tecumseh, 1880-1883 (Box 15, Folder 360)
    - Shipley, George F., undated (Box 15, Folder 361)
    - Shipman, William D., 1881 November 28 (Box 15, Folder 361)
    - Silver, Dilworth M., 1885 January 19 (Box 15, Folder 361)
    - Silver, E. J., 1886 February 2 (Box 15, Folder 361)
    - Sisson, Isaac, 1885 March 17 (Box 15, Folder 362)
    - Smalley, George Washburn (letter of introduction for Sarah Bernhardt), 1880 October 12 (Box 15, Folder 362)
    - Smith, Charles E., 1879 August 18 (Box 15, Folder 363)
    - Smith, Charles S., 1886 December 6 (Box 15, Folder 363)
    - Smith, Edmund H., 1879 June 13 (Box 15, Folder 363)
    - Smith, Henry H., 1895 November 7 (Box 15, Folder 364)
    - Smith, James C., 1879 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 364)
    - Smith, _____ re: International Monetary Conference, 1881 March 16 (Box 15, Folder 365)
    - Snead, Austine, 1880 May 11 (Box 15, Folder 366)
    - Snyder, H. D. H., 1870 August 20 (Box 15, Folder 366)
    - Snyder, William L., 1880 September 17 (Box 15, Folder 366)
    - Southworth, Henry Clay, 1884 March 28 (Box 15, Folder 367)
    - Southworth, T. J., 1885 April 4 (Box 15, Folder 367)
    - Sother, Thomas M., 1881 January 26 (Box 15, Folder 367)
    - Speyer and Company, 1886 July 20 (Box 15, Folder 368)
    - Spiegelberg, E., 1871 June 17 (Box 15, Folder 368)
    - Sprague, Homer B., 1891 April 21 (Box 15, Folder 368)
    - Stanley, E. S., 1880 September 4 (Box 15, Folder 369)
    - Stanton, M. S., 1879 November 25 (Box 15, Folder 369)
    - State Department (United States), J. B. Moore, 1889 August 13 (Box 15, Folder 370)
    - Stephens, Alexander H., 1881 (Box 15, Folder 371)
    - Stetson, Margaret A., 1890 August 21 (Box 15, Folder 372)
    - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin, 1881 June 14 (Box 15, Folder 373)
    - Stokes, William E. D., 1884 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 373)
    - Stone, R. C. Bullion, 1881 (Box 15, Folder 374)
    - Storer, Sarah S., 1875, 1895 (Box 15, Folder 375)
    - Storrs, Richard S., 1895 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 375)
    - Stoughton, Edwin Wallace, 1879 February 3 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - Stoughton, Mary F., 1879 February 4 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - [Strang?], John C., 1880 (Box 15, Folder 377)
    - Strong, Demas, 1879 (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - Strong, John R., 1882 (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - Stuart, H. L., 1891 March 18 (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - Sutro, (Adolph?), 1891 January 12 (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - Swan, J. R., Jr., 1880 (Box 15, Folder 381)
    - Swartz, J. J., 1885 September 8 (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - Swift, John F., 1881 January 20 (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - Talbot, Thomas H., 1885 (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - Tanner, James (enclosing ALS 1879 Nov 11 from Henry Ward Beecher), 1879 November 12 (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - Taunton, Henry Labouchere, 1st baron, 1864 February 22 (Box 15, Folder 384)
    - Temple, M. S., 1881 January 14 (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - Thacher, E(lizabeth) B(aldwin) (Sherman), 1895 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - Thacher, Sherman D., 1891 June 25 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - Thacher, Thomas A., 1885 February 19 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - Thayer, Eli, 1894 February 7 (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - Thompson, Clifford R., undated (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - Thompson, Richard W., 1880 March 26 (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - Thomson, C. H., 1879 October 29 (Box 15, Folder 388)
    - Thomson, James, 1880 (Box 15, Folder 388)
    - Thornton, Sir Edward, 1880 May 29 (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - Thurman, Allen Granberry (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - Tiffey, S. A. W., 1874, 1880 (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - Tiffey, Sarah E., 1880 March 20 (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - Townsend, Edward Davis, 1864 July 19 (Box 15, Folder 391)
    - Townsend, John J., 1884 (Box 15, Folder 392)
    - Townshend, John, 1883 March 6 (Box 15, Folder 392)
    - Tracy, Ebenezer C. (brother-in-law), 1841, 1851 (Box 15, Folder 393)
    - Tracy, Howard C. (nephew), 1894 May 16 (Box 15, Folder 394)
    - Tracy, Jeremiah Evarts (nephew), 1880-1892 (Box 15, Folder 395)
    - Tracy, Martha S. (niece), 1893 September 13 (Box 15, Folder 396)
    - Traders and Travelers Union, Russell P. Hoyt and Abel Crook, 1885 December 29 (Box 15, Folder 397)
    - Tremain, Henry Edwin, 1883, 1886 (Box 15, Folder 398)
    - Trescot, William Henry, 1880, 1885 (Box 15, Folder 399)
    - Tucker, John Randolph, 1881 January 29 (Box 15, Folder 400)
    - Tucker, L. T., 1871 June 24 (Box 15, Folder 400)
    - Turner, Frank I., 1895 (Box 15, Folder 401)
    - Turner, Jabez, 1879 November 19 (Box 15, Folder 401)
    - Turner, Lee and McClure, attorneys-at-law, 1876 June 1 (Box 15, Folder 401)
    - Tweed, Charles H. (son-in-law), 1880-1882, undated (Box 15, Folder 402)
    - Tweed, Harrison (grandson), 1895 July 11 (Box 15, Folder 403)